betconstruct.com 2019-06-19

# Privacy Policy | BetConstruct

##### Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you, as a data subject have a number of rights, which are detailed below. Some of these only apply in specific circumstances and are qualified in several respects by exemptions in data protection legislation. We will advise you in our response to your request if we are relying on any such exemptions.

  * Access to personal data: You have a right to request a copy of the personal information that we hold about you. Should you wish to make such a request, please see the [ **Contact Us**](https://www.betconstruct.com/contact-sales) section for information on how to contact us.

You should include adequate information to identify yourself and such other relevant information that will reasonably assist us in fulfilling your request. Your request will be dealt with as soon as possible.

  *  Correction of personal data: You can request us to rectify and correct any personal data that we are processing about you which is incorrect. We provide you with account settings and tools to access the information associated with your account.
  *  Right to withdraw consent: Where we have relied upon your consent to process your personal data, you have the right to withdraw that consent. 

To opt out of marketing, you can use the unsubscribe link found in the marketing communication you

  * Right of erasure **:** You can request us to erase your personal data where there is no compelling reason to continue processing. This right only applies in certain circumstances; it is not a guaranteed or absolute right.

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy **** practices of such other sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website.
